<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 { text-align: center; }  Open Datasets (Available on ICPSR) Kramer, B.L., Korkmaz, G., Santiago Calderón, J.B., Guci, L. &amp;amp; Robbins, C. Open Source Software: GitHub User and Activity Data (2008-2019). Inter-university Consortium for Political and Social Research.
Kramer, B.L., Korkmaz, G., Santiago Calderón, J.B., Guci, L. &amp;amp; Robbins, C. International Collaboration in Open Source Software: A Longitudinal Network Analysis of GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DSPG</title>
      <link>/dspg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dspg/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 { text-align: center; }  Data Science for the Public Good (DSPG)   
Each year the University of Virginia’s Biocomplexity Institute holds a summer program for training graduate and undergraduate students how to do applied data science. The Data Science for the Public Good (DSPG) Young Scholars program is a summer immersive program for undergraduate and graduate students from across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 { text-align: center; }  Open-Source Software Research Team   
Open Source Software (OSS), defined by Open Source Initiative, is computer software with its source code shared with a license in which the copyright holder provides the rights to study, change, and distribute the software to anyone and for any purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packages</title>
      <link>/packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packages/</guid>
      <description>  /* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 { text-align: center; }  OSS Software Packages    GHOST.jl GHOST.jl, short for GitHub Open-Source Tracker, is a Julia package for targeted scraping of GitHub user and activity data     tidyorgs tidyorgs is an R package that detects and standardizes organizations in unstructured text data     diverstidy diverstidy is an R package designed for detection and standardization of geographic, population, and diversity-related terminology in unstructured text data   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/papers/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 { text-align: center; }  Current Papers Robbins, C., Korkmaz, G., Calderon, J.B.S., and Kramer, B.L. “Measuring the Cost of Open Source Software Innovation on GitHub.” Draft Available. [GitHub Repo.]
Open Source Software (OSS), defined by Open Source Initiative, is computer software with its source code shared with a license in which the copyright holder provides the rights to study, change, and distribute the software to anyone and for any purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/presentations/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 { text-align: center; }  Conference Presentations and Invited Talks  
 A recent presentation of our research on international collabortions on GitHub at Networks 2021 
  2021 Santiago Calderón, J.B., Robbins, C., Korkmaz, G., Guci, L., &amp;amp; Kramer, B.L. “Measuring the Cost of Open Source Software Innovation on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 { text-align: center; }  Core Team Members   Carol Robbins (National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics, Senior Analyst) Ledia Guci (National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics, Science Resource Analyst) José Bayoán Santiago Calderón (Bureau of Economic Analysis, Research Economist) 
   Gizem Korkmaz (Senior Research Scientist, Coleridge Initiative) Brandon Kramer (UX Researcher, Edge &amp;amp; Node)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
